WILSON MACEDO

Ceará, Brazil

wil.macedo.sa@gmail.com +55 (85) 99944-6620

Linkedin Github Youtube

Driven by a passion for technology and innovation, I am an experienced Full-stack Developer with 5 years of diverse expertise in the field. As a Tech Leader, I possess a strong track record of successfully guiding teams and delivering exceptional projects. My proficiency spans various programming languages, frameworks, and tools, enabling me to adapt to any project's unique demands.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

University of Fortaleza, Fortaleza, CE August 2020 - Present

KEY SKILLS

- React and Next.js with Typescript
 Rocketseat Ignite, 2020
- Node, Express.js and GraphQL
- WebAssembly using Golang

CERTIFICATIONS

- Design Essentials (UI/UX), 2019

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Tech Leader

Klever. São Paulo, SP (Remote) May 2021 - Present

- KleveScan: Working with Next.js, Storybook and Redis with API Route to create a blockchain explorer
- Kleverchain SDK: Working with Golang and Unit tests to create several methods to able the creation of blockchain based applications
- Kleverchain SDK Lib: Working with Typescript create a lib to facilitate use of SDK with all types and some functions and classes
- Klever Custody: Working with Next.js to create a platform of a alternative of self-custody
- NFT Shop (Devikins): Working with Typescript and React.js to create a TRX based NFT shop
- Klever Extension: Working with Typescript and React.js to create a multi-chain chrome extension with all blockchain wallet features and dApps methods implementation

Founder - FullStack Developer Progy, Fortaleza, CE November 2020 - Present

• Dashboard: Working with Next.js and new app directory with Tailwind to create a dashboard of public companies of Ceará

- Server: Working with Node.js, Express.js, Prisma and Postgres to create a Restful API
- Mobile: Working with Expo and Styled Component to create a simple view dashboard indicators

Mobile Developer

Orla Soluções, Fortaleza, CE (Remote) December 2020 - May 2021 • Working with Expo and Styled Components to create hibryd mobile apps for constructor companies

FullStack Developer

University of Fortaleza, Fortaleza, CE December 2020 - May 2021

Working with React.js and SCSS

- Working with React Native and Expo for mobile applications
- Working with Node.js and MongoDB

Automation Engenieer Treinee

Habitat Automation, Fortaleza, CE August 2020 - December 2020

- Create UI/UX Layouts
- Development of Crestons and BTicino modules

FullStack Developer

Freelancer, Fortaleza, CE December 2018 – July 2020

- Websites templates with React.JS and Styled components
- Mobile applications using React Native and Styled Components
- Banners and designs for food companies using Photoshop and Figma

Automation Engenieer Treinee

Proteus JR, Fortaleza, CE June 2018 – December 2018

- Development website using PHP and jQuery
- Create UI/UX Layouts